<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Content>
    <Section Header="Last Updated" SectionID="1" Paragraph="February 19th, 2024"/>
    <Section Header="" SectionID="2" Paragraph="NodeDa LLC (&quot;NodeDa&quot;) values its users' privacy and uses third-party advertising services. This Privacy Policy (&quot;Policy&quot;) will help you understand how we collect and use personal information from those who visit our website or make use of our online facilities and services, including Recipedo, our Cookbook app, and what we will and will not do with the information we collect. Our Policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with NodeDa are aware of our commitment and realization of our obligation to meet and exceed most existing privacy standards."/>
    <Section Header="" SectionID="3" Paragraph="We reserve the right to make changes to this Policy at any given time. To stay up to date with the latest changes, please frequently visit this page. If, at any point in time, NodeDa decides to use personally identifiable information on file in a manner significantly different from that stated when this information was initially collected, users will be promptly notified via email. Users will have the option to permit the use of their information in this separate manner."/>
    <Section Header="" SectionID="4" Paragraph="This Policy applies to NodeDa and any subsidiary company listed below, and it governs any and all data collection and usage by us, including Recipedo. By using anthonyjsilvia.com and any subsidiary website listed below, including Recipedo, you are consenting to the data collection procedures expressed in this Policy."/>
    <Section Header="Company:" SectionID="5" Paragraph="NodeDa LLC"/>
    <Section Header="Company Websites:" SectionID="6" Paragraph="nodeda.com, id.nodeda.com, ai.nodeda.com, ux.nodeda.com"/>
    <Section Header="" SectionID="7" Paragraph="Please note that this Policy does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that NodeDa does not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by us. If you visit a website that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information. It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website or app you choose to use or frequent to better understand the way in which websites and apps garner, make use of, and share the information collected."/>
    <Section Header="Specifically, this Policy will inform you of the following:" SectionID="8" Paragraph="What personally identifiable information is collected from you through our website and app.Why we collect personally identifiable information and the legal basis for such collection.How we use the collected information and with whom it may be shared, including Firebase, and Recipedo.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information."/>
    <Section Header="Information We Collect" SectionID="9" Paragraph="It is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any products or services. This website and app collect various types of information, such as:Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information, etc., which may be used when you purchase products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested.Information automatically collected when visiting our website and app, which may include cookies, third-party tracking technologies from Firebase, and server logs.In addition, NodeDa may have the occasion to collect non-personal anonymous demographic information, such as age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race, and religion, as well as the type of browser you are using, IP address, or type of operating system, which will assist us in providing and maintaining superior-quality service.NodeDa may also deem it necessary, from time to time, to follow websites and apps that our users may frequent to glean what types of services and products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.Please rest assured that this site and app will only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide to us through surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site and app to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested, and any additional uses specifically provided for in this Policy."/>
    <Section Header="Why We Collect Information and For How Long" SectionID="10" Paragraph="We collect your data for several reasons:To better understand your needs and provide you with the services you have requested.To fulfill our legitimate interest in improving our services and products.To send you promotional emails containing information we think you may like when we have your consent to do so.To contact you to fill out surveys or participate in other types of market research when we have your consent to do so.To customize our website and app according to your online behavior and personal preferences.The data we collect from you will be stored for no longer than necessary. The length of time we retain said information will be determined based on various criteria, including the relevance of your personal information, our duties and obligations, limitation periods within which claims might be made, retention periods prescribed by law or recommended by regulators, professional bodies or associations, the type of contract we have with you, the existence of your consent, and our legitimate interest in keeping such information as stated in this Policy."/>
    <Section Header="Use of Information Collected" SectionID="11" Paragraph="NodeDa does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent, or lease any of its customer lists and/or names to any third parties.NodeDa may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and app and to ensure the delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from anthonyjsilvia.com and its subsidiaries, as well as Recipedo.NodeDa and its subsidiaries may also be in contact with you regarding completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.NodeDa uses various third-party social media features, including but not limited to LinkedIn, Facebook, TikTok, YouTube, and other interactive programs. These may collect your IP address and require cookies to work properly. These services are governed by the privacy policies of the providers and are not within NodeDa's control."/>
    <Section Header="Disclosure of Information" SectionID="12" Paragraph="NodeDa may not use or disclose the information provided by you except under the following circumstances:As necessary to provide services or products you have ordered.In other ways described in this Policy or to which you have otherwise consented.In the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined.As required by law, or in response to a subpoena or search warrant.To outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential.As necessary to enforce the Terms of Service.As necessary to maintain, safeguard, and preserve all the rights and property of NodeDa."/>
    <Section Header="" SectionID="13" Paragraph="If you have any questions about this Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us by email at privacy@nodeda.com or by mail at:"/>
    <Section Header="NodeDa LLC Attn:" SectionID="14" Paragraph="Privacy Officer 6135 Park South Drive Ste 510Charlotte, NC 28210"/>
    <Section Header="" SectionID="15" Paragraph="We take privacy matters very seriously and will respond to any questions or concerns you may have about our privacy practices."/>
</Content>